<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Battleship Royale</string>
    <string name="credits">By Rafael Cristian Barbieru</string>

    <string name="empezar">Start</string>
    <string name="temas">Themes</string>
    <string name="puntuaciones">Highscores</string>
    <string name="ayuda">Help</string>

    <string name="ok">Got it!</string>

    <string name="info_title">Help</string>
    <string name="info_error_title">Error</string>
    <string name="info_msg_menu">
        - To start the game click on "Start"\n
        - To change the displayed theme click on "Themes"\n
        - To see the highscores click on "Highscores"\n
        - If you need help in any section, you can access to it through the top bar.
    </string>
    <string name="info_msg_prep">
        In this section you have to put your ships on your grid. The way to do it is by
        choosing the type of ship you want to put from the menu on top and click in the
        box where you want to put it.\n\n

        You must use all the ships provided; in order to know how many are left to use you\'re
        given a number next to the type of ship you\'re about to use, in the same menu as the types of ships.\n\n

        When you want to use a ship that\'s larger than one square, you\'ll have to put the bottom of the
        ship on a square and the app will automatically put the rest of the parts on top.\n
        BE CAREFUL! You can\'t put a ship in an already occupied square.


    </string>
    <string name="info_msg_partida">
        Para empezar a jugar el juego tienes que pinchar en "Empezar", tanto desde
        el menú principal como desde la barra superior.
        A continuación deberás elegir la dificultad en la que jugar.
        Se te permitirá posicionar tus barcos y empezará el juego.
        Para atacar a un barco pulsa en su posición en el tablero del enemigo.
        No podrás atacar dos veces en la misma posición.
        Gana el primero que destruya los barcos enemigos.
    </string>
    <string name="info_error_selecciona_barco">
        You have to choose a ship type before you can place it on the grid!
    </string>
    <string name="info_error_posicion_invalida">
        The position you chose doesn\'t allow the rest of the ship to be created!
        Place the ship in a way that there is enough space on the right to allow
        the rest of the ship to be created.
    </string>
    <string name="info_error_no_mas_barcos">
        There are no more ships of this type left!
    </string>

    <string name="seleccionaElBarco">Select the type of ship</string>
    <string name="fragata">Frigate (1 sqare)</string>
    <string name="buque">Warship (2 vertical squares)</string>
    <string name="portaaviones">Aircraft carrier (3 vertical squares)</string>
    <string name="necesarios">Ships left</string>

    <string name="theme_title">Theme selection</string>
    <string-array name="theme_options">
        <item>Basic theme</item>
        <item>Premium theme</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="theme_basic_toast">Basic theme has been selected</string>
    <string name="theme_premium_toast">Premium theme has been selected</string>

    <string name="difficulty_title">Difficulty selection</string>
    <string-array name="difficulty_options">
        <item>Seaman</item>
        <item>Captain</item>
        <item>Admiral</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="titulo_tablero_jugador">Your board</string>
    <string name="titulo_tablero_enemigo">Enemy\'s board</string>
</resources>